粲呀粲\h\h\hJennysueyolo\h\h\h\hPhagee
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
Look at this dick wrinkle.
这是在发什么呆
Where are you taking me to lunch?
中午打算带我去哪吃饭
I have to head over to midtown.
我要去一趟市中心
They find something?
他们找到什么了吗
No.
没有
Just a meeting.
就是见个面
Same shit.
老一套
All right, all right.
好吧  好吧
Tomorrow night, though,
那就明天晚上
don't go fucking bailing on me this time.
别他妈又放我鸽子
It'll be good for you.
对你有好处
Who knows, you might even like this chick.
谁知道呢  也许你会喜欢这小妞
Nah, probably not.
八成不会了
She's kind of hot, though, you know?
但她挺火辣的
Hot in that kind of, keep her eyes open during a BJ
在口活的时候睁眼睛的那种火辣
kind of way, feel me?
你懂我意思吗
- I better get going. - All right.
-我得走了  -行
Here.
给你
What is that, six in a row?
这是什么  连着六个了吗
Eight.
八个
Yeah, well, whatever, dick,
随你怎么说  混蛋
I'm coming for you next month
我下个月再来找你
and you owe me lunch.
你欠我一顿午饭
Oh, um... I'm going to be unavailable for the rest of the day.
今天剩下的时间我都不在了
- Sure, no problem. - Okay.
-好  没问题  -行
Is everything good? Are you okay?
一切还好吗  你没事吧
Yeah.
没事
Finally tracked down the mother.
终于找到了他的母亲
Molly Kirby.
莫莉·柯比
Wasn't any help.
没多大用
Said she hadn't seen him in months,
她说几个月没见过他了
not sure she'd tell us if she had.
就算见了可能也不会告诉我们
What about a roommate?
那有没有室友
Girlfriend?
女朋友呢
I mean, somebody has to have seen him at some point, right?
我是说  总有人在哪见过他吧
The problem is,
问题是
when they've been this close to the bottom for so long,
他们卡在最后一步太久了
it makes it easier to stay under the radar.
要找到他就更难了
While we appreciate you wanting to help,
你想帮忙  我们很感谢
it's best you let us handle it.
但让我们来处理是最好的
Do what you can to move on.
尽最大努力往前看
Hey, I know, okay?
我理解的  好吗
I know.
我理解
But you got to take it from me,
但你要听我一句劝
this shit will eat you up inside.
它会由内而外吞噬你
Consume you all together if you let it.
任其发展  你会什么都不剩
Didn't think people actually ate these.
还以为没人会吃这个呢
Apparently.
显而易见
You know, we have an organic section now, it's--
我们现在设了有机食品区  在
you really shouldn't eat these.
你真的不该吃这个
Honestly, I wouldn't even feed them to a dog.
老实说  我都不会拿这玩意喂狗
Not that I don't like dogs, but like, you know.
不是说不喜欢狗  但你知道的
That's nice.
太好了
Good to see you!
很高兴见到你
Yes, it's always good to see you, Claude.
见到你总是很高兴  克劳德
- Do you salsa? - Hi everyone, I'm Kyra!
-你跳萨尔萨舞吗  -大家好我是凯拉
- Hi. - Welcome.
-嗨  -欢迎
- Waiting on one more? - Yes.
-还有一个人吗  -是的
- You must be Rylee. - Yes!
-你一定就是莱莉了  -对
Oh, Riley with an I, Y two E's.
他是锋利的利  我是茉莉的莉
- Oops. - I know, right?
-巧了  -可不是吗
This is Claude.
这是克劳德
- Hi. - Hi.
-嗨  -嗨
So sorry I'm late you guys.
太对不起了  我来晚了
One of the little bastards pissed himself,
有个混蛋尿在自己身上了
so I can't freaking even,
我都没法抓狂了
how are you?
你怎么样
- Hi! - I'm good.
-嗨  -我很好
Huh, both of you.
你们两个
- Hi, delicious. - So good to see you!
-你好啊帅哥  -见到你真高兴
Good to see you, too!
见到你也很开心
Soria, this is Claude.
索里亚  这是克劳德
Claude, this is Soria.
克劳德  这是索里亚
Claude.
克劳德
Rylee has told me everything,
莱莉什么都告诉我了
and it's just so... awful.
这简直太  糟糕了
It's terrible.
太可怕了
So, no pressure, let's just do a little dance,
别有压力  我们来跳支舞
have a little fun, get down tonight!
玩得开心一点  今晚舞动起来
- Yeah? - Okay, let's get started.
-好吗  -好  那就开始吧
No, go back I think.
不对  我觉得该往后退
Okay, better.
有进步
Maybe just try and feel the music,
试着去感受音乐
don't worry so much about the steps.
别太担心步伐
Or rhythm.
或是节奏
Not bad.
还不错
Not great, either.
但也没有很好
Okay, okay, maybe let's just do a little spin.
好了  我们来做点旋转动作
- Yeah? - Yeah.
-我吗  -对
So we're going to step out
先往外一步
and spin into our partner's arms. Okay?
然后转到搭档的臂弯里
Nice.
很好
Just that easy, ready?
就这么简单  准备好了吗
- Yes. - Okay.
-准备好了  -好
Oh, oopsie, oh, sorry.
错了  抱歉
And five, six, seven, eight.
五  六  七  八
- Fuck! - Oh, you, ah, yeah, that's…
-靠  -你  这
oh, shit, shit, are you all right?
糟了  糟了  你还好吗
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine, fine, fine, fine.
还好  还好  我没事  没事
- Are you all right? - Ah, yeah, s-- shit.
-你还好吗  -还好  靠
Yeah, I think I just, uh, she went a little fast
我觉得我  她数得有点快
- and I missed my count. - Yeah, get her up.
-我数错拍子了  -把她扶起来
- We'll get you up. - No, you guys, stop.
-我们把你扶起来  -不要  你俩别
Up, up, up, up, there we go.
起来  起来  好了
Okay, keep going.
好的  继续走
- Oh, God. - It's okay.
-我的天  -问题不大
Let's get you to sit down.
给你找个地方坐下来
- Okay, ah! - That looks bad.
-好  -看上去挺糟的
- You're so strong. - Oh, yeah.
-你真强壮  -那是当然
We're going to put you right here.
我们扶着坐到这里吧
There we go.
就是这样
Get it, oh, there we go.
就这  慢慢坐下
I'm fine. I'm fine you guys.
我没事  我真的没事
I-- Can I help? Can I get you some ice or something?
我能帮什么忙吗  给你拿点冰块之类的
Oh, no, no.
不用了
Thanks.
谢谢
Okay.
好吧
- Oh, jeez. - Um, maybe, maybe just some Ibuprofen or--
-老天  -能给我点布洛芬吗
Yeah, no problem.
当然  没问题
I'll grab something.
我去拿点
Or just a ride home would be nice.
要是能载我回家就太好了
She's on your way, you should take her.
她和你顺路  你载她吧
Sure, yeah, no problem.
当然了  没问题
Rain check?
改日再来吗
Yeah.
好
How about you two, you want to finish up?
你们两个呢  想继续吗
Uh, well, we're here.
既然我们都在这了
What do you say, Ry Ry, huh?
你觉得呢  莱  莱
Olé!
好耶
- Here you go. - All right, here we go.
-给你  -好的  我们开始吧
Let's go, come on.
来吧  开始
Ah, well that's usually the problem though, isn't it?
通常来说那的确是个问题  是吧
But I am a pretty good judge of character.
但我看人很准的
I can tell a person's appearance just by looking at them.
我可以通过外观来判断他们
- That's impressive. - Yeah.
-很厉害  -那是
What I can't seem to tell is whether they're married or not.
但我看不出他们结婚没有
The last two, oh, maybe three relationships?
我的上两段  可能是三段恋情
All married guys. Can you believe that?
都是已婚人士  你能信吗
I don't know, maybe it's just they're pent-up primal desires
怎么说  也许是因为他们压抑的原始欲望
that I'm attracted to?
我才会被吸引
Or maybe I just have this scent that attracts married guys?
又或者是我有一种吸引已婚人士的特质
I don't know.
我也不清楚
Is this it?
这到你家了吗
Oh, yeah.
是的
Are you in a hurry?
你着急走吗
- Okay. Yep, sorry. - Oh, got it. Okay.
-来  抱歉  -站稳了  没事
- Yeah. - Yeah, it's uh...
-来  -在
it's just all the way... at the top.
在最上面
Yeah, figured.
我想也是
Okay.
好了
- Okay, ooh! - Yeah, okay.
-很好  -很好
Oh, shit.
靠
Maybe if you just, we just power through
你可以  我们可以加把劲
real fast then, huh, yeah?
快点上去
Or not, okay, we'll go slow.
算了  好吧  我们慢慢走
Oh, okay, are you all right?
你还好吗
Okay, I'll put you--
我把你扶到
- Okay, right here is good. - Right there, okay.
-这里就行了  -那里  好的
Okay.
好了
Yeah, yeah, okay.
好了  好了
Okay, so.
到了
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
-谢谢你  -不客气
Did you bang it out?
你上床了吗
Porn?
黄片呢
No, and, uh, no.
没有  不是
- And, uh, no more setups. - Really?
-别再给我牵线了  -真的吗
God, I swear she just smelled horny.
老天  我发誓她闻起来就很饥渴
Oh, well, whatever.
算了  管他的
Can we talk about that instructor, though?
聊聊那个指导老师怎么样
What is that all about?
那是怎么一回事
Ah yeah, you know.
你知道的
Rylee was all like,
莱莉说
"Would you please stop poking me with that thing?
"你能别用那玩意戳我吗
What is your problem?"
你有病啊"
And I was all like, "Sorry, sweetheart,
我说  "抱歉  亲爱的
you're just such a sexy dancer!"
你跳起舞来太性感了"
She didn't buy it.
她没吃我这套
She knew it was strange boner.
她知道就是莫名的勃起
Hey, where are you going?
你要去哪
Uh, I've got a lunch meeting.
我有个午餐会议
- What? - Yeah.
-什么  -是的
Oh, all right.
好吧
Don't mind if I do.
可别介意
Yeah.
看看
Your secret's safe with me.
保证不把你秘密说出去
It's all right.
没关系的
Thanks.
多谢
♪ Ah it's the bait come here ♪
♪ 来这的是诱饵 ♪
- I'm sorry… - Stop.
-对不起  -住嘴
No, listen. Listen, man, you got to let me tell you, okay?
听我说  兄弟  你必须要听我说
- I'm just trying to tell you what… - Stop.
-我只想告诉你  -住嘴
- I'm, I… You gotta let me tell you what I was… - Stop.
-我  你必须听我说我当时  -住嘴
- I didn't, I didn't… - Enough!
-我不是  我不是  -够了
I didn't, I didn't mean to do it, okay, I, s--
我不是  我不是故意的  我
Look, you got to just let me tell you
你必须听我说
what happened! Okay, you got--
发生了什么  你必须
What are you going to do with me, huh?
你想拿我怎么办
You going to keep me down here forever?
你要永远把我关在这里吗
What don't you just fucking get it over with?
你他妈怎么就不能放下
There, there really isn't, but something you know.
真的没有  但你也知道
- But, but, but, I mean… - John?
-但  但  我是说  -约翰
John!
约翰
John, this is, this is what I'm hearing, John.
约翰  我有听说  约翰
I'm hearing that you don't trust me, John.
我听说你不信任我  约翰
- That's what I'm hearing. - No, no, no, that's not.
-我是这么听说的  -不不不  不是的
No? -No, I'm telling you.
-不是的  -不  你听我说
No, no, stop.
不对  不是的  打住
- But it just, I'm going to try-- - Stop, listen.
-但我要试着  -停下来  听着
John, this, this is what I want you to do.
约翰  我想让你这么做
I want you to call every shop in town, John.
我要你给镇上所有的商店打电话   约翰
I want you to take copious fucking notes, John.
我要你他妈的做充足的笔记  约翰
And, and, find that magic, hocus pocus fucking deal, okay?
然后  试试能不能做成神奇的生意
And when you realize that it doesn't exist,
当你意识到这根本就不存在时
and that what I'm offering is legit,
我的报价才是合法的
then I want you to call me back
我希望你那会给我电话
so I can tell you to fuck off, John.
然后我就可以跟你说滚开  约翰
- Oh, is that so? - You know, you know what? Yeah--
-是吗  -你知道吗  是的
since I'm a busy guy, I'm going to save us both the effort.
我挺忙的  我们俩都省省力气吧
Fuck off, John.
滚开  约翰
You know what? You're right, you're right.
知道吗  你是对的  你完全正确
The offer's fair, I trust you.
提议很公平  我相信你
You've been a straight shooter with me and I,
你一直对我直言不讳
- I'll tell her we're going with you. - Good.
-我告诉她我们和你一起去  -很好
Then send in your shit.
把你的东西发过来吧
You should ask her out.
你应该约她出去
Who?
谁
What, the instructor?
什么  那个指导老师吗
Yeah, Kyra.
是的  凯拉
Kyra, Kyra.
凯拉  凯拉
Uh, oh, Kyra, oh, oh, Kyra!
哦  凯拉  噢  噢  凯拉
Just saying her name gives me a fucking mouthgasm, dude.
光说她名字我嘴巴都能高潮  伙计
I was so mad at Ry the other night,
前几天晚上我很生莱的气
I started thinking about her while we were having sex.
我们做爱的时候  我开始想她
Oh, it was nice.
感觉还不错
Super quick, though. Um, just in, out... right on her stomach.
超级快  进来出去  射在她肚子上
- Ugh, how do you, how do you-- - What,
-你怎么  怎么能  -怎么了
oh, dude, that shit goes both ways.
老兄  这玩意是双向的
Trust me, that's why it works.
相信我  这就是为什么会有用
I promise you, as far as she's concerned,
我向你保证  就她而言
I was Channing fucking Tatum digging her out,
我是他妈的查宁·塔图姆给她新生
going deep, giving her the old Magic Mike.
越来越深入  给她来个原版《魔力麦克》
I don't care.
我不在乎
You know, you, you are like some kind of
你知道吗  你  就像某种
poetic yet filthy savant, you know that?
有诗意但下流的学者  你知道吗
Whoa, I like that.
我喜欢这说法
Come on, ask her out.
来吧  约她出来
- Not happening. - Ugh, come on dude, I know it's weird
-不可能  -伙计  我知道有点奇怪
and there's some unwritten rule,
还有一些不成文的规定
but I, I got to say man, half the time I don't know
但我得说  跟你在一起有一半的时间
what to say or how to act around you.
我不知道该说什么  该做什么
In fact, what I do know is that I am of zero help
事实上  我确定的是  大部分的时候
or comfort to you most of the time, all the time!
我都无法帮助你  宽慰你  一直都是
Ugh, dude, you are fucking miserable.
伙计  你他妈过得很苦
And she wouldn't want it like that.
她不会愿意你这样的
Hi... Hi.
你好
-Hi. - Hi.
-你好  -你好
Claude, right? Friend of the Rileys?
克劳德对吗  莱利夫妇的朋友
Yeah, that's me, yeah.
是的  是我
So, can I help you?
那么  有什么需要我帮忙的吗
Yes, yeah, um, yeah, I, I was, um,
是的  有的  我
I was thinking about, um, getting back in to it, maybe?
我在想  或许能回到这里来
You know, uh, just, just, uh, just a couple of lessons.
你明白吗  就  上几节课
Lessons, you want salsa lessons?
上课  你想上萨尔萨舞的课吗
Yeah or, um, you know I-- I've always been interested in the,
是的  我一直对这个挺感兴趣的
um, the foxtrot.
狐步舞
Foxtrot?
狐步舞吗
- Uh, that's a shame. - It is?
-真可惜  -是吗
Yeah, I mean after you pussed out the other day
是啊  我是说你那天开车路过
and did that whole duck and cover drive away thing?
赶紧低头  开车过去的事
I thought maybe this time you'd, uh, sacked up to ask me out.
我想也许这次你会  鼓起勇气约我出去
What?
什么
No, I didn't, what are, I, I, I didn't.
不  我没有  什么  我  我没有
- I did. - You did.
-我有  -你有
I did, yeah, I, that--
我有  是的  我
um, would you, would you like to have dinner with me?
你愿意  你愿意和我一起共进晚餐吗
Sometime, um, in the, in the near future?
在  在不久的将来
Yeah, I would.
好  我愿意
Sometime in the near future.
在不久的将来
Okay.
好的
- Well? - Molly Kirby?
-怎么了  -莫莉·柯比是吗
You got her.
是我
I wonder if I could talk to you
不知道能不能跟你谈谈
about your son, Logan?
你的儿子  洛根
Look, I done told you,
听着  我已经告诉过你们了
motherfuckers, I haven't seen him.
混蛋  我没有见过他
I'm not with the motherfuckers.
我和那些混蛋不是一起的
You're a real funny asshole, huh?
你真是个有趣的混蛋
I just want to talk.
我只想和你谈谈
I'm sure you're not fucking shocked to find out
我敢肯定你他妈的一点都不惊讶
that I wasn't the most nurturing of mothers, hm?
我不是那种典型的母亲  对吗
Tough love, you know? It's good for kids.
严厉的爱  知道吗  这对孩子有好处
What about the, uh, his dad? Is he still around?
那他父亲呢  还在吗
You're fucking kidding, right?
你他妈的在跟我开玩笑  是吗
Is this some sort of talk show shit?
这是什么狗屁脱口秀吗
You're right.
你说得对
Just line them up and point and, uh, there you go.
让他们排一排  随便指一个  就是了
Call Maury. Congratulations, you are the father.
打电话给莫里  恭喜  你是父亲了
What about as a kid?
那他小时候呢
What was he like?
是什么样子的
What was he like as a kid?
他小时候是什么样子的
I don't fucking know. He was a fucking kid!
我他妈的不知道  就是个孩子
What are you writing, uh, a biographical or something?
你在写什么  传记什么的吗
Hm? You, you got some rich guy guilt?
是那种有钱人的内疚  是吗
- No, I'm not, um, I'm not, uh, writing-- - Well then what the,
-不  我没  没在写什么  -那什么
what the fuck?
那你他妈的是在干什么
What are you after?
你想怎样
I--
我
I don't know.
我不知道
What, are you lonely?
怎么  你是孤单吗
Because that's maybe something I can help with.
如果是这样  或许我能帮上忙
No.
不是
No, thank you.
不用  谢谢
He says, "No, thank you."
他说  "不用  谢谢"
You are a funny asshole.
你真是个有趣的混蛋
You still haven't told me why you're looking for him.
你还没有告诉我  你为什么要找他
Logan, he, um...
洛根  他
He--
他
I'm wasting my time.
我在浪费时间
Hey, oh, what's your name?
等等  你叫什么名字
It's Claude.
我叫克劳德
Hey, buddy.
嘿  伙计
Got John's package back.
把约翰的包裹拿回来了
It's a big one.
是单大生意
I'm proud of you.
我为你骄傲
Great, thank you.
很好  谢谢
Just, uh, double check the signatures and...
只是  再检查一下签名
...um, leave it on my desk.
放到我桌子上
All right. Okay.
好的
Ah, there he is! Yeah, yeah, what, what!
他在这  棒呆了  是不是
I got to run, I'll call you later.
我得走了  稍后给你打电话
Oh, oh, oh, bro, I need a solid!
伙计  我要你帮个忙
Wife's got us going to this wine and paint bullshit tonight,
老婆让我们今晚去那种红酒油画的地方
I need a wing man. You ever heard of that garbage?
我要人当托儿  你听说过那种地方吗
I can't, not tonight.
不行  今晚不行
Brother, it's wine and painting!
兄弟  有红酒和油画
What if I grow a vagina? Please,
要是我长出个阴道呢  拜托
- please, please, please, please. - I have a...
-求你了  求你了  -我有
- Please. - ...I have a thing.
-拜托  -我有点事
- A, a thing? - Yeah.
-有点事  -是的
Like a, like a thing thing?
是真有事的有事吗
Yeah, a thing thing.
对  真有事
Oh, with who who?
那是和谁呢
Kyra.
凯拉
I'm sorry. Oh, I'm so sorry.
对不起  我很抱歉
It technically, um, technically this is, uh, this is fusion.
严格来说  这是  这是融合餐厅
- Uh-huh. - Yeah. I, uh, I read that, um,
-是吗  -是的  我读到过说
that-- that fusion is... good for first dates.
这种融合餐厅最适合初次约会
Good for first dates, you, you read that?
适合初次约会  你读到过
Online, yeah.
在网上  是的
It's, it's really stupid. It's so dumb.
这  这太傻了  太蠢了
So, um, your friends.
那么  你朋友
- The Rileys? - Mm-hm.
-莱利夫妇吗  -是的
They're weird.
他们很奇怪
They really, really are.
他们真的  真的太奇怪了
I got the feeling
我有种感觉
that I was the subject of some masturbatorial ritual.
我成了某种手淫仪式的对象
- Is that a word? - I, I think so, yeah.
-是这个词吗  - 我想是的
I think so, or it should be and, uh, you were.
我想是的  或者就应该  是你
Oh, God, it's flattering, right?
天哪  这是奉承吗
I don't know, I, you know, he,
我不知道  我  你知道  他
he masturbates to those, um,
他能对着那些东西手淫
to those hamburger commercials,
那些汉堡包的广告
Oh, my God. -so--
我的天哪
Okay.
好吧
You know, my ex was like that.
你知道  我的前任喜欢那样
I used to catch him, like, every other day.
我以前每隔一天就能抓他一次
Really?
真的吗
Really. We used to go through paper towels by the dozen.
真的  我们以前纸巾一打一打地买
Always in front of a mirror.
总是在镜子前面
- Fetish thing. - Fetish, um, the, the paper towels?
-是恋物癖  -是恋  纸巾吗
No... the mirrors.
不是  是镜子
A nightmare in fitting rooms.
试衣间里的噩梦
Yikes.
好吧
It was cato-something-philia.
是反射什么什么症
Married and divorced within a year.
一年内结婚又离婚
How about you, ever married?
那你呢  结过婚吗
Yeah.
有过
Okay and?
好的  然后呢
You know all about my pud whacking ex.
你都已经知道我前任的破事了
Out with it.
说出来吧
What, divorced?
怎么  是离婚吗
Did it get ugly?
撕逼撕得很厉害吗
Oh, lesbian?
是女同性恋吗
Come on, please tell me she went taco!
拜托  告诉我是因为她疯了
Yes? So, what did she go butchy
是吗  所以  她是很肌肉猛女
or like TV porn pretty?
还是像色情片里一样好看
She passed away.
她去世了
Oh, shit. Ah, shit.
妈的  该死
I don't, I don't know what-- I don't what to say, um--
我不  我不知道该说什么了
Tell me you're joking, you--
告诉我你是开玩笑的  你
You're fucking with me?
你在耍我吗
Oh, my God.
我的天
Um, how long?
多长时间了
Eight months.
八个月了
Eight? This, uh--
八个月  这
Is, is that enough time?
时间够长了吗
Well, I, I don't know. Um.
这个  我不知道
I don't know if there's uh, like a,
我不知道是否有
you know a set, like a set or, or definitive.
一个期限或是  确定的时限
No, no, no, no, okay, I'm sorry.
不  不  不  好吧  我很抱歉
I'm sorry, I, I'm just really bad at this.
对不起  我真的很不擅长这个
And I, and I, um...
我  我
Could we, could we just get out of here?
我们可以  可以走了吗
Okay, yeah, yeah, no problem.
好的  好的  没问题
No, no, no, no, I, I still want to hang.
不  不  不  我还想再一起待会
I mean if you do.
我是说如果你愿意的话
It's just, I, I fucked this up,
只是  我搞砸了
and, and the smell of this fusion.
还有这融合餐厅的味道
- And, and the lesbian thing, and-- - Yeah, honestly, look,
-还有女同性恋的事  -说真的  听着
um, there's, there's no way you could have known.
你不可能提前预料到的
Okay.
好吧
Um, I'm sorry, you, you had something else planned?
抱歉  你  你还有什么别的计划吗
Yeah, I, yeah.
是的  我
Get out of here though.
还是离开这里吧
As a kid, when I'd get all messy, my dad
小时候  我吃东西糊了一嘴时  我爸爸
would always like lick a napkin
总会把纸巾舔湿了
and wipe my face with it.
来擦我的脸
Oh, yeah, I remember that. And the, uh,
是的  我记得这种事  还有
this smell of his own spit.
他自己口水的味道
And, ugh.
恶心
It must be like a...
这一定是
A weird, instinctual dad thing, yeah?
怪怪的  作为父亲的本能  对吧
- Hm. - Yeah.
-是的  -对
Yup, that's it!
对  就是这样
Thank you very much for helping me relive that trauma.
非常感谢你帮我缓解了那种恶心
This date, bad food, ice cream,
这个约会的糟糕食物和冰激凌
I feel like I'm 15 and you're going to try
让我觉得我只有15岁
and fill me up at any minute.
你随时都想尝试和我来一发
Nah, I, I, I thought, um, a bit of nostalgia would be fun.
不  我认为来点怀旧会很有趣
Mm-hm. So, what's next, putt putt and making out
那么  接下来干嘛  上车
on the Kingdom of the Dinosaurs ride?
在去恐龙王国的路上亲热吗
Ah, second date.
第二次约会
Hm, that's usually when I go for boob, too.
通常到那会我才会想要摸胸
So, you're safe tonight.
所以你今晚很安全
Hm.
好啊
Wow, that you know, it used to take me like hours
你知道吗  以前我常常需要花好几个小时
to work up to that kind of courage.
才能鼓起这种勇气
I feel so cheap.
我觉得好廉价
- I'm sorry. - No.
-对不起  -不
Here you go.
给你摸
Go on.
来啊
Just a quick feelsy, only fair.
公平起见  就很快地摸一下
Yeah?
好了
That's it?
就这样
How was it?
感觉怎么样
- It's good. - Good?
-还不错  -不错
Great, it was, um, awesome.
很棒  感觉特别好
Awesome boob, very, very enjoyable, yeah.
极品胸部  非常令人愉悦  对
How was mine?
我的如何
Small little bee sting.
像被蜜蜂蛰了一下
like a handful, big nipples.
手感很好的大乳头
Well, uh, thank you for the throw back.
谢谢你送我回来
You're welcome, yeah.
不客气
You all right?
你还好吗
Yeah, you're welcome.
嗯  不客气
- You said that. - Yeah.
-你已经说过了  -对
Look, I get if it's too soon.
如果是因为进展太快  我可以理解
No, no, no, no, um, it's not.
不不  没有
Um, in fact, I'd like another try.
其实  我想要再试一次
Hm, something edible, next time?
下次来点好吃的
I'll think about it.
我会考虑的
Thank you.
谢谢
Man, you okay?
嘿  你还好吗
Yo, hey, I'm sorry, look, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
嘿  对不起  对不起  对不起
Hi.
你好
Hey. I had a date tonight.
嘿  我今晚去约会了
And, and I en-- enjoyed it.
我还挺乐在其中的
And I feel awful.
对此我感觉很糟
Yeah.
好吧
Um, I, uh, I visited your mother.
我去看了你母亲
My, my mother?
我母亲
You, you visited her, what, what's that mean?
你去看了她  什么意思
She's...
她
...she's interesting.
她挺有趣
Interesting?
有趣
You going to call her?
你会打电话给她吗
- Should I? - For sure, yeah.
-我应该吗  -当然了
Isn't there, isn't there some kind of rule?
是不是有什么规则
Nah, nah, man, nah. See that's, that's some old school shit.
不不  那些规矩太老派了
You should call her.
你应该打给她
Hey, how's, how's my mom?
嘿  我妈怎么样
Good.
不错
Worried about you.
挺担心你
Yeah.
好吧
Hey, hey, dude, do you mind
嘿  伙计  你介意
the TV maybe?
给我看会电视吗
Here.
给
And what am I, what am I supposed to do with this?
我拿这个  我拿这个能干嘛
Yes, yes, I, I deserve that.
对  对  我活该
Sure, yeah, yeah, I'm up for that.
当然  好的  我会去的
Okay.
好
Yeah, I, no, I'll swing by, mm-hm.
好  我会顺路过去的
Okay, easy enough.
好的  很简单
Okay, all right, I'll see you then. Okay.
好的  没问题  回见  好
All right.
好的
Hey!
嗨
Look who's off the dog food... Remember?
看看这谁  都不吃狗粮了  还记得我吗
Yeah.
嗯
I guess so, yeah.
我想是的
Thanks to you.
多亏了你
Aw, really?
真的吗
Awesome.
太好了
At least there's progress.
至少有了进步
You called her?
你给她打电话了
She did.
她打的
So you've dance before?
所以你以前跳过舞吗
Uh, a little. Yeah, I'm a little rusty, you know.
一点点  你懂的  我有点生疏了
Yeah, I thought so.
我也这么想的
Yeah. Decent moves.
动作做得挺好
And you can always tell by someone's walk
你总是可以从一个人的走路姿势
if they have rhythm.
判断出他懂不懂节奏
So what was it, ballroom?
所以你学过什么舞  社交舞
Tap, maybe?
或许是踢踏舞
A little.
一点点
Hip hop mostly.
主要是街舞
Fuck off.
操
Real life B-Boy.
真实生活中是嘻哈男孩
Shut up, you're such a liar.
闭嘴  你骗人
No, no. A little popping, locking.
没有  一点点机械舞和锁舞
Okay, challenge.
好啊  我挑战你
Challenge accepted.
我接受挑战
Is that a C Walk?
这是C步吗
Yeah.
对
Yeah, you know, gangsta.
你懂的  帮派舞
You know, just, uh, hustling the streets.
你懂的  道上混的
Trying to earn that dollar.
想挣点钱
Uh, it was, um, yeah, it was, uh, just for girls,
这  是为了赢得
and to impress girls.
姑娘们的欢心而已
Is that right?
是吗
- Is it working? - A little bit.
-那么奏效了吗  -一点点
Good, you know, because usually,
太好了  因为通常
actually after I, um, after I do something like that
其实在做完这些动作之后
I'm like, "yo girl, you want to freak this?"
我就问"嘿美女  你想来段磨舞吗"
Freak?
磨舞
I completely forgot about freaking.
我完全不记得磨舞怎么跳了
Oh, yeah, hm.
啊对哦
Hold that thought.
等一下
See what you got.
让我来看看你有什么本事
Mm, yeah, get in there.
对  多吃点
Does freaking always make you this hungry?
跳磨舞会让你这么饿吗
Yeah, it's why I was so fat in high school.
对  这就是为什么我高中的时候那么胖
Huge.
体型庞大
I'm just glad they didn't have that intervention show back then.
我很庆幸以前没有那种强制演出
You know, because my family would have been like,
因为我家里人就会说
"Claude, we love you,
"克劳德  我们爱你
but we're worried about your freaking.
但我们很担心你的磨舞
It's really gotten out of hand."
有点失去掌控了"
Same here, but mine would have been for anal.
我也一样  不过手掌换成肛门
My mom was pretty protective.
我妈妈的保护欲特别强
No, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding.
不  我只是开玩笑
She didn't care. Loved the butt stuff.
她不在乎  喜欢这些和屁股有关的东西
No.
是的
Well, again, sorry about that.
再次表示抱歉
That's all right.
没事
Now we know why I choose restaurants and the movies.
现在知道为什么我选择去餐厅和电影院了
Deal.
成交
Coming in, you weirdo?
进来吗  你个怪胎
I'm all out of Boone's Farm.
我没布恩农场的酒了
Regular wine okay?
普通的红酒可以吗
Ha, perfect, yeah.
可以  完美
So, how long have you had the studio for?
所以你拥有工作室多久了
I have had the studio for two years, Claude.
我这个工作室已经两年了  克劳德
And is it, um, something, you, you, always wanted?
有没有什么是你一直想要的
Yeah. Yeah, I always wanted to own a shitty
有  我从小就一直想有一个
little dance studio since I was a little girl.
小小的舞蹈工作室
Life goal, complete.
人生目标达成了
So, it's going well? Um, you
所以一切都进展得很顺利  你
Just stop.
别说了
That's plenty. You can just.
有很多  你可以
Are you okay?
你还好吗
I'm sorry.
对不起
Oh, my God, are you, are you?
我的天  你是不是
I can't.
我做不到
Oh, my.
我的天
How's the book?
书怎么样
It's not bad now that I'm getting' used to it.
还不错  我渐渐读进去了
It's a book that she was reading when I saw her.
我见到她时  她就在读这本书
The book, um, the first time I saw her, she was reading it.
我第一次见到她时  她读的就是这本
That, that book.
就这本书
Well, you know, this, this is the first book that I ever read.
知道吗  这是我这辈子读的第一本书
As in like, the first time I ever read any book.
是我这辈子第一次看书
You know, that wasn't like a kiddie book or something.
你懂的  不是儿童读物之类的书
It felt like I was, uh, cheating on her.
我觉得我出轨了
She was there, and...
她坐在那里
...she's on my lap,
她坐在我腿上
and all I can think about was her.
我脑子里只有她
Yeah.
好吧
You know the, um, the first girl I ever got with
你知道吗  我第一次上床
was this red-haired chick named Martha.
是和一个叫玛莎的红发小妞
And normally I-- I am not into shit like that, but you know,
通常  这不是我的菜  但你知道
but Martha she was like, like, damn.
玛莎她简直是没话说
And I was like, whoa.
然后我就  惊呆了
Skin all creamy and shit.
皮肤那么光滑细腻
And I-- I didn't know what I was doing,
我不知道我在干什么
but you know, Martha she knew some things.
但是玛莎知道
Yeah, she knew some things.
她懂的
But like ever since her it's all been downhill.
但自那以后  感觉就没那么好了
It was like nobody is good enough.
似乎没有人足够好到能满足我
You know, nobody has that magic touch.
你懂吗  没人可以让我有那奇妙的感觉
So, finally I just, I started asking girls
所以后来我就开始让别的女孩
to do things like Martha would do.
做玛莎会做的事情
You know, I, I wouldn't say like,
你知道的  我不会直接说
"Hey, do it like Martha's doing it."
"嘿  像玛莎一样做"
But I would like kind of instruct them.
但是我会耐心引导她们
But, you know, Martha was always there,
但是  玛莎一直都在
in my head when I was with the others.
当我和别人搞的时候一直在我的脑海中
So.
就这样
Yo, I think you got problems.
我觉得你要有麻烦了
What?
啥
The detective guy is here to see you, ha ha!
那个探长来找你了
So, do you like being a detective?
所以  你喜欢当侦探吗
Detective McGee?
麦吉探长
- Been that long? - A few years, yeah.
-有那么久了  -对  有几年了
Hey, so did you find something or...?
所以你是找到什么线索了吗
Got a call from Molly Kirby.
我接到了莫莉·柯比的电话
Right. She, um, said you stopped by.
是的  她说你去看她了
Got the impression you were from our office.
她觉得你是我们警方的人
She got, I didn't tell her that.
她是  我没这么跟她说过
Why were you there?
你为什么会去她那
- I don't know. - You don't know?
-我不知道  -你不知道
I don't.
我不知道
Look I get, uh, confused.
听着  我很迷茫
anxious, and, and, and--
很焦虑  还很
frustrated that you know, you guys haven't.
沮丧  你们就不会
She said you threatened her.
她说你威胁她了
What, no.
什么  没有
No, absolutely not!
没有  绝对没有
What's that about?
那是怎么回事
What's what?
什么怎么回事
I got a bag in the garage.
我的车库里有个拳击袋
Just letting off a little steam.
只是发泄一下
Right.
好吧
Well, uh, you should get some gloves.
好吧  你应该带副手套
You just left, nothing, not a word?
你就那么走了  连句话都没留
Mm, no, I, I, I, um.
我  我  我
I, I might have mumbled something,
我  我可能嘀咕了两句
and, and, and then it's all kind of a--
然后  然后  就好像
But like her stuff was out, right?
但她亮出胸器了  对吗
I...
我
...might have been crying.
我可能哭了
But her skin was soft?
她的皮肤柔软吗
Her body tight, like dancer tight?
身体像舞者那样紧实吗
Hm, I'm sorry, that's totally fucked up. I'm sorry.
抱歉  我胡说的  很抱歉
That's terrible, it's terrible.
这太糟了  太糟了
- The crying, I mean... - Yes, yeah, I know.
-你哭了  我是说  -好了  我懂的
- Thank you. - It's terrible.
-谢谢  -太糟了
You want some noodles, maybe?
也许  你想来点面条吗
Make it better.
会让你感觉好些
♪ Noodles make you happy ♪
♪ 面条带给你欢乐 ♪
Oh, hey.
你好啊
Hey. Hi.
你好
Hey, I'm, I'm so sorry about the other night.
那天晚上的事  我很抱歉
No, you, you, you don't have to, um, apologize at all.
不  你完全用不着道歉
I'm sorry.
应该是我感到抱歉
Um, you're, uh,
你
you're wonderful.
你真的很棒
And I'm, um, I'm yeah, I'm, I'm, I'm,
然后我  我  我
I'm pretty fucked up right now and,
我现在一团糟
I like, I, I don't even--
我  我甚至不知道
I get it.
我懂
I really like you, though.
其实我真的很喜欢你
I like, I mean, I really like you.
我喜欢  我是说  我真的喜欢你
- Yeah? - Yeah.
-是吗  -是的
Yeah, but I, you know,
是的  但是我  你知道的
I'd understand, you know,
我理解的  你懂的
if af-- after that.
如果在那之后
The crying?
你是说你哭的事吗
So I was actually crying?
所以  我真的哭了
Yup.
是的
- Oh, God. - It was kind of cute.
-我的天啊  -还挺可爱的
- Really? - No.
-真的吗  -并不是
But, you know, maybe it'll make a good story someday?
但  也许有一天会是个好故事
Yeah, something to relive over and over and over again.
是啊  值得一次一次地回味
So...
所以说
...do you want another round?
你还想再试一次吗
That is if I promise not to try and have sex with you?
要是我保证不试着跟你上床的话
I think that's agreeable, yeah.
我觉得这样挺好  我愿意
Then it's a deal.
那就这么说定了
Deal.
说定了
I finished the book.
我读完了
Cover to cover.
从头至尾
It feels kind of good.
感觉不错
Yeah, I think I know what you mean. Like,
我知道你的意思  就是
you know, when the, when pages get thinner on one side
翻页的时候  看过的越来越多
and fatter on the other.
剩余的越来越少
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
对  就是那样
I mean, I don't understand most of the shit,
我是说  大部分我都没太理解
but like... there's some funny ass females yo.
但是里面有些女性很有意思
And them be like, like, they fucked up, too,
她们也  也会搞砸
but like in a way
但从某种程度上讲
that makes you say like I get you. You know?
就好像在说  我懂你  知道吗
And that fucking Nancy, right?
那个操蛋的南希  对吧
Wait, I don't, I don't remember a Nancy.
等等  我不记得有什么南希
Nancy.
南希
- The author? - Yeah, her.
-作者吗  -是啊  就是她
Oh, my god, dude, she's just like bam, bam, bam, bam, bam,
兄弟  她像是  啪  啪  啪
just like dropping one gem after another.
丢下一颗又一颗的宝石
And she's kind of mean, but like,
她有点刻薄  但是
like sassy, too, so it's sexy.
很时髦  也很性感
And they supposed to be all hoity toity and shit,
他们本应都是自命不凡的家伙
but they like fucked.
但是他们喜欢做爱
They fucked. All the way.
一直不停地做
Kind of tells you about people, huh?
透漏出什么是人性  是吧
Yeah.
是啊
She's wild, man.
她挺野的  兄弟
Wow!
天啊
You weren't kidding.
你没开玩笑吧
I have to warn you, I am very, very good at this.
我得提醒你  我很擅长这个的
- Yeah, sure. - Mm-hm.
-真的吗  -是啊
What is that?
你拿的什么
This is, um...
这是
...my putter.
我的推杆
You bring your own putter?
你带了自己的推杆来
It's better than the rentals.
这比租的好
No, no way, put it back.
不  没门  放回去
What, why?
为什么啊
Who brings their own putter to miniature golf?
谁会到迷你高尔夫场带自己的推杆
No, no it's embarrassing!
别这样  太丢人了
No, come on, it's not embarrassing.
不会  拜托  这并不丢人啊
I would rather sit in front of those teenagers
我宁愿坐在那些青少年对面
with you weeping on my breasts again,
让你趴在我怀里哭
before being seen with a man who brings his very own
也不愿被人看到和一个自带推杆的男人
grown-up putter to miniature golf.
一起迷你高尔夫
- Oh, well done! - Thank you.
-打得好  -谢谢
Uh, uh, uh, no, no.
不  不能这样
What?
为什么
You follow that through, there are no gimmes.
你得打完  还没到自由推杆
All right, PGA, is that how we're doing this?
好吧PGA  我们照这规矩打吗
You did say you were good, right?
你说过你很擅长  不是吗
♪ When the madness Rings our ears ♪
♪ 当我们耳边响起了疯狂 ♪
♪ I just want to have you ♪
♪ 我只想占有你 ♪
It's pretty good, though.
还挺不错的
♪ Tell me that you want to ♪
♪ 告诉我你也想要 ♪
♪ With your spark That turns to gold ♪
♪ 让你的火花变成金色 ♪
♪ And your eyes that ♪
♪  你的眼睛 ♪
♪ Bare your soul ♪
♪ 展露你的灵魂 ♪
♪ Does it really matter ♪
♪ 这真的重要吗 ♪
♪ Tell me what you're after ♪
♪ 告诉我你想要什么 ♪
♪ Lights out, baby now ♪
♪ 现在就关灯  宝贝 ♪
The hole is this way.
洞在这边
♪ You're mine, Don't fall behind ♪
♪ 你是我的  别落后了 ♪
♪ I love to feel you all over ♪
♪ 我想要感受你的全部 ♪
Miss!
中不了
Miss it!
打不中
♪ Don't care what you do ♪
♪ 不管你做什么 ♪
♪ I'll light the fire Inside of you ♪
♪ 我会点燃你的心火 ♪
Hit the ball!
击球
♪ And we can make an explosion ♪
♪ 我们一触即发 ♪
If you get this, I will...
如果这个球你中了  我就
♪ Even when You've gone too far ♪
♪ 即使你走得太远 ♪
♪ Will always have my heart ♪
♪ 我都会守住你的心 ♪
♪ I will hold you closer ♪
♪ 靠近你 ♪
- Thank you! - You're welcome.
-多谢  -不用客气
What?
怎么了
You are, um--
你真是
you are really bad at math.
你数学真不怎么样
We tied.
咱俩平局
- Yeah. - Oh, what?
-是的  -什么
Tiebreaker, biatch!
再来决胜局  混蛋
All right, tiebreaker.
好吧  决胜局
♪ Don't care what you do ♪
♪ 不管你做什么 ♪
♪ I'll light the fire Inside of you ♪
♪ 我会点燃你的心火 ♪
♪ And we can make an explosion ♪
♪ 我们一触即发 ♪
♪ Lights out, baby now ♪
♪ 现在就关灯  宝贝 ♪
- Yes! - Oh, you didn't.
-棒  -你不是吧
- Beauty! - Get out of here.
-干得漂亮  -走吧
♪ Don't care what you do ♪
♪ 不管你做什么 ♪
♪ I'll light the fire Inside of you ♪
♪ 我会点燃你的心火 ♪
♪ And we can make an explosion ♪
♪ 我们一触即发 ♪
Oh, look at those tiny nipples!
快看他的小乳头
Oh, stop!
快住嘴
Awesome time. Sorry you lost.
玩得真开心  抱歉你输了
Oh, yeah, I'm sure you are, yeah.
是啊  我知道你是真心道歉
You know, if I, if I'd only had my putter--
如果我用了自带的推杆
You'd be a sad, sad lonely man with no friends.
你真是个没朋友的小可怜
I don't know. I think, um, think
我不知道啊  我想
that little kid, I think he was
我内心住着个小孩
into me. He winked, I think.
他眨眼了
- No. - Mm-hm, yeah.
-不是吧  -是的
I missed that.
我漏了这茬
Thank you.
谢谢
So, uh, Riley's having a birthday party tomorrow night
莱利明晚要办生日派对
and, technically, I don't have to get him a present
严格来说  如果带你去的话
if you were to show up with me.
我就不用准备礼物了
Look at you.
瞧瞧你
First pimping me out to the golf kid
先是拉我和高尔夫小哥的皮条
and now this.
现在又来这个
And I'd really like it if you came with me
我真的很希望你来
and I got to spend another night hanging out with you.
这样就又能和你一起玩一晚上了
Okay then.
那好呀
Damn it. I must really, really like you, too.
见鬼  我肯定也很喜欢你
Because I've had actual nightmares about him
因为我做了关于他的噩梦
and the things he might do to himself.
梦见了他可能对自己做的事
Then thank you.
那先谢谢你
Peace out.
撤了
I've been busy.
我一直很忙
It's one of my favorites.
这是我最喜爱的其中一本
It's thick.
好厚
- Yeah. - Nice.
-是啊  -很好
I'm telling you, I mean seriously dude,
跟你说  我认真的  兄弟
if my wife--
如果我老婆
- Shh... - What, oh.
-嘘  -怎么了
- Hi. - Hi.
-你好  -你好
Kyra tells Tattianna and I
凯拉告诉我和塔蒂安娜
that you are quite the dancer.
说你舞跳得好
She's exaggerating.
她夸张了
- No, I'm not. - Yeah, she is.
-不  我才没有  -不  她就是
You have moves.
你有自己的动作
- Downright freak this one. - Oh, freaky!
-这家伙可会磨舞了  -磨舞啊
Okay, drinks, drinks, refill?
好吧  再来一轮  好吗
Mule, Cosmo,
莫斯科骡鸡尾酒  大都会鸡尾酒
Cosmo, Goose and tonic, yeah?
大都会  灰雁伏特加和汤力水  对吗
- Riley, why don't you come join me? - What?
-莱利  你来帮我吧  -干什么
I've got two hands and we need four drinks, so.
我只有两只手  但我们需要拿四杯
Okay.
好的
Come on.
快来
Seriously, you guys are like a perfect match.
说真的  你俩超般配的
Oh, no, we're just chilling. You know, with his stuff.
不是啦  我们就是放松放松
Oh, my god, I know. And he's like the best.
天啊  我知道  他是最棒的
Like, literally the best guy ever. Like, literally...
简直就是史上最完美的人
and his wife...
还有他妻子
...so super-duper great, too.
也是个超级大好人
- Oh, you, you knew her? - Mm-hm.
-你认识她吗  -是的
Yeah, we, we haven't really talked about it.
我们还真没聊过这事
I think it's too much for him.
我觉得这对他来说承受的太多了
Well, I just hope they find that fucker.
我只希望他们能找到那个混蛋
I'm sorry, what? Uh, who?
抱歉  你说什么  找谁
The guy, you know?
就是那个家伙
They haven't caught him yet.
他们还没捉到他
To think he's still out there.
一想到他还在四处游荡
Claude is like an angel,
克劳德就像个天使
because I would be out there
要是我  就会带把枪
with a gun like, seriously.
遇上了就真准备用
Ladies.
女士们
Thank you.
谢谢
I think I spilled on myself.
我好像溅到身上了
At least now, you know, we'll both be having nightmares.
至少现在  我们都会做噩梦
Honestly, I've never even seen them like hold hands,
说实话  我从未看到他们牵手
let alone doing whatever they were doing.
更别说他们做的其他什么事了
- You okay? - For sure.
-你没事吧  -没事
Are you sure?
你确定吗
Yeah, I just, uh,
我只是
Tattianna was telling me about your wife.
塔蒂安娜跟我说到了你妻子
I am so sorry.
我很抱歉
Well, you could have just asked me.
其实你可以直接问我
No, I didn't, she just started going, I didn't ask her.
我没问  她就说了  我没有问她
Right.
好吧
I wanted you to know that I want to be here.
我想让你知道现在有我在
However long it takes you,
不管多长时间
I want this.
我想这样
Yeah?
是吗
Yeah.
是的
Okay.
好
Can we just, um,
我们能
can we just talk about Riley for like, one more second?
我们能再谈谈莱利吗  就一小会
Please?
拜托了
I'm sorry, I didn't want to think about him just now.
抱歉  我现在不愿意想他的
I really didn't, but it's just what he pulled back there,
我真的不想  但他之前做的那些动作
it's just come on.
真是见鬼了
- Come on, drink up.  - Ah, God bless you.
-快点  喝了  -谢谢你
- You'll feel much better.  - Was it embarrassing?
-你会好点的  -昨天很尴尬吗
Hi.
嗨
- Good morning.  -Ah, yes it is.
-早上好  -成了
Where do you think you're going, Mr?
你要去哪  先生
- Stop.  - I want to know everything.
-停下  -我想知道所有细节
I think you've got a story to tell.
我觉得你得讲个故事
- Stop, stop! - Hey, what, what, what, what?
-停  停  -嘿  怎么了  怎么了
So?
所以呢
So.
所以
So we, we, we hung out all night, and--
所以我们在一起度过了一晚上
We binged watched some TV shows and we ordered pizza.
我们看了很多电视节目还点了披萨
And?
然后呢
- No. - No?
-没有  -没有吗
We're…
我们
We're waiting.
我们还在等
You're waiting?
你们还在等
- You're waiting? - Yeah.
-你们还在等  -是的
Okay.
好吧
You know, actually, um,
你知道  这真的
actually, I think that's kind of sweet.
还真的  有点甜
You do?
你真这么想的
Yeah, I do.
是的
What, I do!
怎么了  真的
I mean, I, I like romance and shit, too.
我其实  我也很喜欢搞浪漫的
You know?
你知道吗
And, ah, I'm, uh, I'm just happy that you're happy, man.
我  你开心了我也跟着高兴  兄弟
Oh, man, I, I'm so sorry,
兄弟  对不起
- I should have, I should have been there for you. - What?
-我应该  我应该陪着你的  -什么
With the whole wine and paint thing.
那次喝红酒画画
Because look at you, you went ahead and you...
看看你吧  你变了
...you grew a vagina.
你长出阴道来了
Oh, you fucker.
你个傻逼
Yeah, right, but like, I'm, I'm thinking
是的  对  但  我在想
he's a straight fucking perve, you know? Like, sick.
他简直就是个变态  什么毛病
Uh, uh, he's just sitting there
他就坐在那
watching, getting a boner and shit?
看着  然后勃起了吗
What the fuck is that?
都他们的是些什么
And, and, okay, look, he's funny as shit, I'll give you that.
但 但  他还挺好玩的  我同意
But, like, I got a little sister, you know?
不过  我有一个妹妹  你知道吗
I didn't know.
我不知道
- No. - Yeah, man,
-不知道  -好吧  兄弟
so I, I, I can't get down with that.
所以我  我不能接受这个
You know?
知道吗
Yeah, I think you have to read it a couple of times.
好吧  我觉得你得多读几遍
Yeah, at first it's pretty graphic, yeah.
是的  一开始是很形象  确实
Oh, fuck it, I got the time, right?
他妈的  我确实很有时间  对吧
I read it every couple of years.
我隔几年读一次
Changes every time.
每次感觉都不一样
There's a movie, too.
这部书还拍成了电影
They made a movie?
拍成电影了吗
How the hell did they ever make a movie out of this?
这玩意是怎么拍成电影的
I don't know, man. Look, like what if you were a dad?
我不知道  兄弟  如果你是个父亲
Now you'd beat the shit out of him, right?
你会狠揍他一顿  对吗
Look, I am not the most accomplished journalist and shit,
听着  我不是最好的记者
but if my…
但如果我
Hi, surprise.
嘿  惊喜吧
- Yeah. - Well, I was hungry and I wanted to see you.
-确实  -我饿了而且我想见你
That okay?
可以吗
Yeah, yeah, of course.
当然  当然可以
Oh, look a hot girl just kissed me and brought me dinner.
看啊  辣妹亲了我  还给我带了晚餐
I better stand outside looking
我还是站在外面
like an idiot and smiling.
像个傻子一样  笑着就好
Would you like to come in?
你想进来吗
- Yeah, thank you. - Oh, then please come in.
-当然  谢谢  -进来吧
- Kitchen? - Kitchen's that way.
-厨房  -厨房在那边
More?
再来点
Yeah.
好
So, how was your day?
今天过得怎么样
It's good, it's fine.
挺好  挺好
It's just sort of,
就是一些
work stuff, hm. You?
工作上的事  你呢
-Yeah, mm-hm. -Everything good?
-挺好  -都挺好的吗
Yeah?
是吗
Well, I was just thinking about that promise I made you,
我只是在想我答应你的那个事
about not, um--
那个不
I...
我
...have an, oh,
有
see? I just knew they were in there.
看  我就知道在那
Better?
好多了
Yeah.
是的
Yeah?
是吗
Oh, yeah.
好
Oh, hey, is this okay?
这样可以吗
- Yeah. - Because I, I don't, I don't want to rush you.
-当然  -我  我不想太着急
Okay, yeah, thank you, thank you.
没事了  好了  谢谢  谢谢
- So, stop? - No, no.
-所以停了吗  -不  不
No? Absolutely not.
不  当然不能停
You okay?
你还好吗
- Yeah. - Because we can just cuddle if you want to.
-当然  -如你愿意  我们可以只抱抱
- No, absolutely not. - Sure, okay.
-不  当然不  -好  来吧
Hey, hey, hey, no, no, no! Wait, wait, hey, hey, hey.
嘿  嘿  嘿  别  等等  等等
Wait, no, no, no, no!
等等  别别别
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等  等等
Get the fuck away from me!
离我远一点
Wait, wait,
等等
wait, Kyra, Kyra, Kyra. Wait,
等等  凯拉  凯拉  凯拉  等等
wait, please, just, just listen.
等等  听我说
Just listen, I'll explain.
听着  我给你解释
I'll explain, I'll explain,
听我解释  听我解释
I'll explain. Please, please.
求你了  听我解释
I, I um…
我  我
I, he, he's, it's him.
我  他  他是  是他
He's the guy.
就是他
I, I caught him.
我  我抓住了他
The man, um, the man you just, you just saw?
那个男的  你刚刚看见的那个男的
He's, um, he's, he's the one, he--
他是  他是那个  他
he… he killed... he killed my wife.
他  他  他杀了我的妻子
I tracked… I see, okay, I tracked him down...
我抓住了  好吧  我抓住了他
- Don't. - ...and he.
-别  -然后他
I didn't know what to do, okay?
我不知道该怎么做  好吗
- I, I, I was, I was… - You did, you did what?
-我  我  我  -你  你干了什么
- You tracked him down? - I just, I just,
-你抓住他了  -我只是  我只是
okay, can we, can you just come back in for like one second.
好吧  我们能  你能回来我们谈谈吗
- Can you come back in, we'll talk. - No.
-你能回来吗  我们谈谈  -不
- He's the guy? - Yeah.
-就是那个人吗  -是的
- This is so fucked, Claude. - I know.
-这他妈太操蛋了  克劳德  -我知道
- Really? - I know, I know, I know.
-是吗  -我知道  我知道  我知道
Can we just talk?
我们能谈谈吗
Talk? I'm not having this conversation!
谈谈  我才不会和你谈呢
You're torturing a person in your basement!
你在地下室折磨一个人
- I… I know, I… - What are you doing?
-我  我知道  -你在干什么
What, are you just keeping him?
怎么  你就这么关着他吗
- I don't, Kyra… - What?
-我没有  凯拉  -什么
I should have just stayed the fuck away from you.
我他妈的应该远离你
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
好了  好了  好了  好了
Can you just, um, can you just come back in for one second?
你能  你能回来我们就谈一会
- Come back? - And we'll talk for one second.
-回来  -我们就谈一会
Talk about what?
谈什么
I'll explain, I'll explain everything.
我会解释的  我会解释所有事情
Explain? It's pretty clear.
解释  已经很清楚
Son of a bitch, Claude, I can't! I…
混蛋  克劳德  我不能  我
Fuck, I have to--
操  我必须
What if it was you?
如果是你呢
I didn't know.
我不知道
What would you have me do? I…
你让我应该怎么做  我
I didn't know what to do!
我不知道该做什么
I didn't know, please.
我真的不知道
What am I supposed to say to that, Claude?
我应该说什么呢  克劳德
What?
什么
I'm supposed to be flattered?
难道我应该感到高兴吗
No, no, I was, I--
不  不  我  我
You have a man chained up in your fucking basement,
你在你地下室里关着一个人
Claude, that's not exactly happily ever after for me.
克劳德  于我这可不是从此就幸福快乐了
Kyra.
凯拉
Did you... what did you say to her?
你  你对她说什么了
- Look, I didn't say anything. - What did you say?
-我什么都没说  -你说了什么
I swear to God, I didn't say anything to her!
我发誓  我什么都没说
- What did you say her? - No, no, no, no!
-你对她说了么  -别  别  别
Do it.
杀了我
Do it, do it, do it, do it, do it.
杀了我  杀了我  杀了我
Do it, do it, do it!
杀啊  动手啊
Do it, do it!
动手  动手啊
You fucking coward! You fucking coward!
你个懦夫  你个怂货
You fuck…
你他妈的
You took, took her from me.
你把  你把她弄跑了
You took, you took, you took...
你  你  你
...took her from me.
让她离开了我
You want to talk about it?
你想谈谈吗
You good?
你还好吗
What?
什么
Yeah.
很好
Whatever, yeah.
没什么  我很好
Really try to channel the artist's vision.
尝试感受画家的视线
I think I'm going to jump off the bridge.
我想我要从这桥上跳下去
Capture his determination.
理解他的目的
This was supposed to be fun.
那应该很有趣
His passion.
他的那份热情
Why did he choose this subject?
他为什么选择画这个
Why are you here, right now recreating it?
你为什么会在这  在这重新创造它
Sipping wine.
喝着红酒
- Powerful. - I thought so myself.
-很有力  -我自己也这么认为
Are you done? Are you done?
你说完了吗  你说完了吗
Good. Uh, that is a
很好  那是个
very interesting strategy
有趣的策略
and considering that
鉴于此
I am absolutely confident that you are way too
我又觉得的信心  你实在
fucking stupid for me to help.
蠢到让我无法帮忙
All the best.
祝好
Let's go, they're waiting.
走吧  他们等着呢
Come.
来吧
This is anti-climatic.
这太反常了
I know, I know, he's never there.
我知道  我知道  他从来不在
We're all standing around
我们都在这站着
- like we don't know… - All right.
-好像我们不知道  -好了
- Is he coming? - Yeah, he was just on the phone.
-他来了吗  -来了  他刚才打电话呢
- There he is. - All right, are we all here?
-他来了  -好  都到齐了吗
Thank you, slow poke, okay.
谢谢你  磨蹭蛋  好了
Another big year folks!
又度过了很棒的一年
You guys were amazing!
你们都很棒
Seriously, oh, oh, that's weird.
说真的  这有点奇怪
There's something, I'm sorry,
这有什么东西  抱歉
there's something scratching.
这有什么东西刮着我
I don't know what that,
我不知道这是啥
oh, that's weird, it's a check.
真奇怪  是张支票
Did you put that in?
是你放进去的吗
- No. - No, okay, that's weird.
-不是我  -不是  好吧  真奇怪
Oh, it's for $15,000.
是15000美元
and cheering
欢呼吧
That is a nice… Oh, oh, my God.
这真是超棒  天呐
- What? - Is there something? Do you see any?
-怎么了  -有什么东西  你看到了吗
I have this weird thing sticking out of my--
有什么奇怪的东西卡在
Yeah, it's here. It's like caught on my Spanx.
对  在这  卡在我的塑身衣上
Yeah, there's something. All right.
对  是了  好了
Oh, this!
这个
I remember, okay, I remember I put this in my,
我记起来了  对  我记得我放在我的
all right, two tickets for an all-expense paid trip to
好了  两个费用全包的旅行名额  去
- Hawaii! - Hawaii!
-夏威夷  -夏威夷
♪ Hawaii, Hawaii ♪
♪ 夏威夷  夏威夷 ♪
Oh, my goodness.
我的天
So, you know, just a little something to congratulate
你们知道的  一个小礼物送给
number one sales person of the year. Wonder who that could be?
年度最佳销售员  好奇是谁呢
There's no suspense, look, this person has had a rough year.
不卖关子了  这个人今年过得很艰难
Right, we, we can all acknowledge that. I mean,
是吧  我们  我们都看得到
he's been through some things
他经历了一些
that we can't even imagine, and...
我们甚至都无法想象的事
...the thing is he, he persevered, you know?
但重要的是  他克服各种困难撑下来了
And he showed up every single day and he kicked some ass,
他不仅每天来上班  还做得很出色
and that's-- that deserves some applause.
这值得大家为他鼓掌
This person is someone to be admired.
这是个值得钦佩的人
Claude Vaughn, where you at? Where is he?
克劳德·沃恩  你人呢  他在哪
Get over here! Yeah!
快过来
Give it up
掌声响起来
for our number one sales rep!
给我们的销售第一名
-Come on down.  - Claude, Claude,
-快过来  -克劳德  克劳德
Claude, Claude, Claude, Claude.
克劳德  克劳德  克劳德  克劳德
Come take the tickets.
快来拿你的票
You got it. Woo, hoo!
你可以的
Now you get your spanking!
现在你收获一份打屁屁奖励
I'm going to spank you!
我要打你喔
No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding,
没有  我开玩笑  我开玩笑的
that would be harassment.
那可是性骚扰了
All right.
好了
- Ah, there you go. - There it is.
-戴上了  -戴好了
- Number one, number one! - Yeah, buddy.
-第一名  第一名  -太棒了 兄弟
Congratulations.
恭喜
Great job.
真棒
Who would have thought it'd take something like this
谁能想到经历了这些
for me to get clean, huh?
才让我戒了毒瘾
I can't even remember the last time.
我都不记得上次吸是什么时候了
I needed money, I wanted--
我那会需要钱  我想要
I wanted money.
我想要钱
To score.
去买毒品
It was-- It was getting pretty bad.
事情  事情开始变得很糟
We were, we were supposed to be in and out.
我们  我们本来打算拿了钱就出来
And I saw her standing there
然后我看到她站在那
off to the side.
站在边上
She didn't look scared, or nothing.
她看上去并不害怕  或怎样
She had nice stuff.
她看起来挺有钱的
You know, big bag, big rings.
你知道的  很贵的包  很大的钻戒
So I walked over to her.
所以我走了过去
She was real pretty.
她真的很漂亮
I snatched her bag and I say, "Give me the fucking rings."
我抢过她的包  然后说"把戒指给我"
She wouldn't do it.
她不愿意
She wouldn't do it, she--
她没给  她
It just made me mad.
我就来火了
She made me real fucking mad, man, so I said,
她把我惹毛了  所以我说
"Give me the fucking rings,"
"他妈的把戒指给我"
and I'm pointing my gun in her face.
我用枪指着她的脸
I was just trying to scare her, man.
我真的只是想吓吓她
I swear to God I was just trying to fucking scare her.
我发誓我他妈真的只是想吓吓她
Fuck.
操
Hey, well, fuck it, you know.
太操蛋了
There are no, there are no excuses.
但这不是借口
Do what you got to do, man.
你想怎么处置我都行
I get it.
我都理解
Do what you got to do.
随你处置
I'm just going to take some time.
我想休息一段时间
Maybe use those tickets.
或许把那两张票用了
-Good. - There's just a--
-没问题  -就是
a few things I've been pushing off for a little too long.
有些我一直拖着没做的事
You're right, well,
你说得没错
you know what? That office is going to be waiting for you
知道吗  你的办公室会一直给你留着
whenever you're ready.
无论什么时候你想回来
And you know what, maybe even a bigger one.
甚至换一间更大的
I appreciate that.
我很感激
Next time not next to the shitter.
下次肯定不会在厕所旁边了
That'd be nice.
那最好了
-Okay. We'll see you. - Ah, okay.
-我们会再见的  -好的
- Okay. - Ah, yes, it's nice.
-好了  -这感觉很好
All right, thanks. Thank you.
好了  可以了  谢谢
We're going to miss you. Oh.
我们会想你的
Okay. We're still going to chill, right?
我们还是能一起出去玩的  对吧
Yeah, yeah, of course.
当然  当然
Okay. Okay.
那就好
All right buddy, we'll see you.
好的兄弟  我们回头见
Hold me.
抱我
No?
不要吗
She's clean, she drives pretty well, she's a little banged up,
车很干净  也好开  只是撞了一下
but, uh, you want to take her for a test drive?
不过  你要不要试驾一下
Hey, look at you!
看看你今天买的
I'm so proud.
真为你骄傲
Thank you.
谢谢
I need you to listen to me.
我要你仔细听我说
As far as I know, you died in that basement.
于我  你已经死在那个地下室了
Thank you for...
谢谢你
...not calling anyone.
没有告诉任何人
I didn't know how to...
我当时不知道应该怎么
...tell you,
告诉你
that I-I-I had my...
那个  我  我  我
wife's...
杀了我妻子的凶手
...murderer.
在我手上
You know, or what you'd think of me if I did.
如果如实告知  我很担心你对我的看法
Yeah, tough one.
我明白  很难的选择
I thought about calling.
我想过打电话
You, not the police or anything.
打给你  不是报警或什么别的
That's not true, I almost called.
骗你的  其实我差点就报警了
It's hard to digest.
实在太难以接受了
I mean I tried to understand it.
我尝试着去理解你
And then I just think that you're an insane person.
然后我觉得你是个疯子
Yeah.
是啊
Been there.
我也曾经这么觉得
And?
然后呢
He's gone.
他消失了
I-I-I let him go.
我  我  我放他走了
The Rileys came in for another lesson.
莱利夫妇来上了一次课
Got in a fight and left.
大吵了一架然后走了
I mean, they bought
他们买了
like a dozen lessons, so.
很多节课  所以
I think she might get--
我觉得她可能
I got these tickets and stuff to Hawaii.
我有两张去夏威夷的票
I won them at work.
公司奖励我的
It's seven days, and massages, the whole works.
一共7天  有按摩什么的  一整套
Fish, scuba.
钓鱼  潜水
I'm thinking about going next week.
我想着可以下周去
Next week?
下周
I've never been to Hawaii.
我还从来没去过夏威夷
Me neither.
我也是
- Sounds nice. - Yeah.
-听起来很棒  -是啊
Are you-- are you asking me to go to Hawaii with you?
你  你是在邀请我一起去夏威夷吗
Yeah.
是啊
Okay.
好啊
Okay?
真的吗
-They match. - Absolutely not.
-配了一套  -绝对不要
- What? - No, no.
-干嘛  -不行  不行
-It's Hawaii. - Don't be that guy.
-那可是夏威夷  -别穿成那样
What, should I pack my grass skirt?
怎么  那我是不是应该带上草裙
Point taken.
有道理
Okay, you know, if you did have
好吧  如果你真的有
a coconut bra, though,
椰壳胸衣
I think I'd be interested in that.
我觉得我会感兴趣的
Oh, yeah?
是吗
Hm, no room.
行李箱位置不够了
It was that or the edible panties.
要么椰壳内衣要么可食用内裤
Good choice, because I get hungry on planes.
真会挑  我上飞机上就会饿
I get swamp ass.
我很容易湿的
Yeah, we're going to beeline straight for the water, then.
那正好可以直接喝了
- Okay. - Yeah.
-好的  -好
Oh, hey, do you have any of those, um...
对了  你有没有那种
...masky tubey things?
带管子的面罩
Masky tubey things? Snorkels?
带管子的面罩  潜水呼吸面罩吗
- Snorkels, yes! - Yeah, I think I got, um--
-呼吸面罩 对  -有  我记得我
- Get new ones? - Let's get new ones.
-买新的吧  -那就买新的
- Mm-hm. - Yeah, okay, cool.
-嗯  -好  就这么办
Yeah, new ones. Okay.
好  买新的
Let's get out of here, ready?
我们出发吧  好吗
- You ready? - Yes.
-你准备好了吗  -准备好了
Okay.
好的
Morning.
早啊
Good morning.
早上好
I, uh...
我
Going on a trip?
要去旅游吗
Yeah.
是啊
Uh, Hawaii.
去夏威夷
Uh, Detective McGee, this is, this is Kyra.
麦吉探长  这是  这是凯拉
Uh, Kyra this is, um, Detective McGee.
凯拉这是麦吉警探
He's handling, uh, uh, the case.
他是负责案子的
Hi, nice to meet you.
很高兴认识你
You got a minute?
你有时间吗
Okay, sure, yeah.
当然
Please.
请进
How you been?
你最近怎么样
Fine.
挺好的
Never called.
没见你打给我
I've been taking your advice.
我听从了你的建议
Good.
很好
How's your hand?
你的手怎么样了
Better.
好多了
Hm, taking a break.
这段时间没练了
Hitting the bag, right?
打沙袋  对吧
Right.
对
Can I see it?
我能看看吗
The bag, yeah. Yeah.
那个沙袋  当然可以
Follow me.
跟我来
No gloves.
没戴手套
Think I could get a glass of water?
我能喝杯水吗
Yeah.
好的
How long you two been, uh?
你们在一起多久了
- Not long. - A few months.
-不久  -几个月吧
That's good.
那很好
- Detective-- - Can I ask you where you were last night?
-探长  -我能问问你昨晚在哪吗
Yeah, we went out to dinner and then a film.
我们昨晚出去吃晚饭还看了电影
Where?
在哪儿
High Misty and they were playing "Dirty Dancing" at the park.
嗨雾餐厅  然后在公园看了《热身舞》
Anyone else with you?
还有别人跟你们一起吗
Yeah, my friends, the Rileys.
有  我的朋友  莱利夫妇
Mitch, what is this all about?
米奇  你问这些是要干嘛
Found Logan Kirby's body last night.
昨晚我们发现了洛根·柯比的尸体
Shot twice in the chest.
胸口中了两枪
Seems like we weren't the only ones looking for him.
似乎我们并不是唯一在找他的人
Weird thing was, though, it seemed like he was,
不过  奇怪的是  看起来他被
I don't know, tortured.
怎么说  虐待过
You know anything about that?
你知道这事儿吗
No?
不知道吗
How about you?
那你呢
No.
不知道
Well, all that is what it is now.
那好吧  事情就是这样了
I mean, these types get themselves
我的意思是  他们这种人
into all sorts of trouble.
总是会卷进各种各样的麻烦
But murder, that's a different game.
但是杀人  那就性质完全不一样了
Lord knows I'd understand, but I got to ask.
上帝明白我能理解  但我还是得问
Did you murder Logan Kirby?
是你杀了洛根·柯比吗
I wanted to.
我之前想的
But I couldn't do it.
但我下不了手
Have a good vacation.
祝你们假期愉快
You okay?
你还好吗